

Contact

Muriakelvin@gmail.com

© 0700095477

Nairobi

in LinkedIn Profile

Education Background

2022 - 2023 Software Engineer | Moringa School

> Here are four of my <u>Github</u> projects that are still in the works: <u>Events Manager</u>, <u>Moringa Daily-Dev</u>, <u>Task Tray</u>, <u>Movies</u> <u>project</u>

2013 - 2019
Bachelor of Economics and Statistics |
Kenyatta University

Soft Skills

- Great communication skills
- Strong decision maker
- Acute attention to detail
- Computer literacy
- Innovative
- Good business acumen

Volunteer Service and Leadership

- Vice Chairman Sprout Charity Foundation
- Welfare treasurer Akiyda 2000
- Head marketer -Aberdare Institute of Management

References

Available Upon Request

KELVIN HURIA

Software Developer | Accountant

About Me

I am a software engineer with a background in accounting and computer hardware. I have recently completed a comprehensive course, honing my skills in JavaScript, Ruby, React, and Ruby on Rails. With over three years of experience as an accountant, I bring a unique blend of technical and financial expertise. I am known for consistently delivering high-quality work and exceeding expectations.

Coding Skills

- React JS
- Javascript
- Ruby on Rails
- Next JS
- HTML & CSS

Past and On-going projects

Events Manager - Live Link

<u>A</u> mock web application to gather and present forthcoming events in a user-friendly manner, facilitating effortless event discovery.

Technologies used:

- Front-end: React
- Back-end: Ruby on Rails
- Database: SQLite
- CSS Framework: Tailwind CSS

Moringa Daily-Dev - Live Link

A mini web application for the Moringa Community that enables users to get authentic and verified articles/blogs about the tech space created by the Moringa school community

Technologies used:

- Front-end: React
- · Back-end: Ruby on Rails
- Database: Postgres
- CSS Framework: Tailwind CSS, Daisy UI

Movies project - Live Link

Task Tray - Live Link

Professional Experience

Accountant | Bura Communications Limited

April 2021 - March 2022

ICT Technician | Cognisive Ventures

June 2019 - February 2021

Accounting Clerk | Akiyda 2000 LTD

February 2016 – April 2018